It has begun!
Meter related to spectator machines
Ascending TV
Yay!
Ascending!
Yes, so we have been playing a lot of games lately.
This time, they have prepared another game for us.
This time we are going to play
The game of connecting words to the regular rules!
Yay!
It's a little difficult to hear just this,
Pasin pasin nani nani, pasin pasin nani nani,
It's a game where you have to proceed with other games,
For example, the subject is dog on top, so panpan, and when I say dog on top, next panpan,
If you say "Inu-jo", the next Panpan is "Inu-jo".
If the theme is "Inu-kami," you put a letter on top of the word "Inu" (dog),
You are not allowed to try to make either word.
For example, if the word is "inu-kita", you can say "inu-kita panpan" or "inu-kafu panpan".
You have to make sure that the word is a word that exists in the world.
We are trying our best to keep the rhythm of the game going.
If I couldn't think of anything, I would do it.
At any rate, we should try not to break the rhythm.
That's what makes it so difficult.
The first subject is a game.
Games?
I'll start.
What if we start a game?
I'll start the game first.
It's hard.
You're on top, aren't you?
Left hand like this.
That's how it's done.
So you're going to change the subject.
I see. Now I get it.
That's what I'm saying.
Well, let's do it for practice.
To practice.
Then, let's go.
Game on.
Big game, up and down.
Awww...
Say three.
Big game,
Pompon, strawberry up.
Raspberry,
Pom-pom, panda down.
Pong-pong, panda man.
Pom-pom, Strawberry Bottom.
Pompon-Pompon, Strawberry Flame.
Pompon, Flame here.
Gorilla Under.
Gorilla natto.
Awww, awww, awww.
www. www. www. www. www. www. www. www. www. www. www. www. www. www. www. www. www. www. www. www. www. www. www. www. www. www.
Don't say anything important.
Don't say it's important.
It's important because it's Keidai.
Don't say important.
Don't say anything important.
Don't say important things.
It's so difficult.
You just did it.
What's not working?
Sure, I did.
But did you get it?
Pio first?
Hey!
On Life.
That's fun!
LOL!
Laughing
LOL!!!
I went live!
Dresses that look cute live!
Dancing back
I did the windows! We did the windows!
Back up!
Buck! Buck!
Bakudan-do!
We're live!
It's fun live!
And shido!
Bakugan!
LOL!
Live music clubs.You know, like a live music club.
Or something.
LOL.
On camera
Digicam
Ooh!
Socks
on mandarin oranges
Sweet oranges
cosmetics
rabbit
Cosmetics brand
on mandarin oranges
Pop Canning
Lemon Soup
Lemon Choki-chan
On PC
Sorcerer Computer
Pure
Sorcerer PC
From the front of the pen
with you
I've been with you
I'm with you
I'm with you.
When I'm with you
Water
Natural water
Iced
iced water
SQUEEZE
Weather
Flashlight done
Flashlight is important
That was my fault.
I don't know the answer.
I did curry.
I got curry.
Hair coloring
Negative
On bread French bread
On electricity Flashlight
Above mullet Pretty mullet
Below Julia Julie Julie
On poshat Moving poshat
Pappa-pappa-pappa.
Pon chee to three chee hoo
Marshmallow cheese
By the hair
Head Spy
With Cheese
Natural Cheese
Cheese
This is difficult
This is hard!
That's it, that's it, that's it.
You know, I'm just trying to make it easy for you.
It's easy for them to understand.
That's right.
It's difficult.
It's hard.
I don't think I've ever seen so many words.
It's hard to come up with a theme, too.
Yes, it is.
Watch the reference video.
They're all in this game.
Like comedians.
It's all coming out so fast.
I'm working on my acoustics.
Try it.
You know how hard it is.
I've been doing this for light match time and everything.
Somehow.
That's good.
So, thank you for watching.
Thank you very much.
Bye-bye.
Go to the bottom of the channel
Subscribe to our channel
Like us! down
down!
and
Like this! Up.
Lots! Good!
Likes! Bottom
Like it! I'm waiting!
Waiting! Down.
I'm waiting! Messy.
Comment down!
Please!
Comment down!Comment below!
Thank you!
Thank you for watching!